<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://blog.codedlovely.net/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://blog.codedlovely.net/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-05-05T12:54:36+09:00</updated><id>https://blog.codedlovely.net/feed.xml</id><title type="html">CodedLovely Blog</title><subtitle>A note about what I have learned so far.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Hello World</title><link href="https://blog.codedlovely.net/blogging/2022/05/05/hello-world.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello World" /><published>2022-05-05T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2022-05-05T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>https://blog.codedlovely.net/blogging/2022/05/05/hello-world</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://blog.codedlovely.net/blogging/2022/05/05/hello-world.html"><![CDATA[<p>It seems that the rainy season has come in Okinawa. It’s a little chilly even when I’m indoors, but some children with a lot of energy are playing at the outdoor swimming pool.</p>

<p>I’ve been working on this blog for the last couple of days, and finally launched with subdomain of codedlovely.net. I built this blog from scratch while referring to the Jekyll official documentation. Ah, this sense of accomplishment ☺.</p>

<p>Next thing I’m going to do is adding categories to posts and creating archive pages by category. Well, archive pages are meaningless until I publish multiple posts under multiple categories, so it will take time to display those pages on this blog.</p>

<hr />

<p>These days I’m exploring the music genre called “raudo-rokku (loud rock)” in Japan, a type of rock music, since for some reason it appeared in my Spotify recommendation weeks ago. Though I’ve never been an avid rock music fan, I think I’m developing a taste for this kind of music.</p>

<hr />

<p>By the way, I found this quote on the internet. It’s funny and so true, I think I should write it down here.</p>
<blockquote>
  <p>“Light travels faster than sound. This is why some people appear bright until you hear them speak.”<br /><span> - Alan Dundes</span></p>
</blockquote>

<p>See you <i class="fa-solid fa-hand-spock"></i></p>]]></content><author><name>Ai</name></author><category term="Blogging" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems that the rainy season has come in Okinawa. It’s a little chilly even when I’m indoors, but some children with a lot of energy are playing at the outdoor swimming pool.]]></summary></entry></feed>